http://www.back2form.net/index.php/all-about-me/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
TreatmentsWhen to Seek HelpFor HorsesFor Dogs and CatsTherapies UsedWhat to ExpectWith HorsesWith Dogs and CatsFAQsTestimonialsAboutMy BackgroundAreas CoveredTreatment CostsPrivacy PolicyContact MeContactLinks
Privacy Policy (relating to practise)About Us
Jess Harkness, trading as Back 2 Form.
The Purpose of this Notice
This notice is designed to help you understand what kind of personal information is collected with regard to my services, what it is used for and how it is stored.
What is Personal Data?
Personal data is information relating to an identified or identifiable person. Examples include an individual's name, age, address, date of birth, gender and contact details. I collect your name, address, and contact details as part of my record card taking. Back 2 Form may contact you by email/ private messaging on social media, or telephone to follow up on enquiries, making appointments, sending you courtesy reminders for future appointments, or sending invoices. These methods of contact are in your interest and are considered a legitimate means of communication with you to provide a smooth-running service.
Personal Data Collected
In order for me to provide a thorough Physical Therapy service for your animal(s) I will collect personal data to enable the service to be provided. This will be collected either verbally or electronically via email / other forms of messaging. This data will only be shared with your animal's Veterinary Practice to obtain consent for treatment as legally required. A post treatment report may be sent to your veterinary surgeon. Any personal data will be kept in a locked filing cabinet, in a locked room or on a password protected file on a password protected computer.
Why Do I Need Your Personal Data
Your personal data is required to identify the animal to be treated to the Veterinary Surgeon. It is also needed to keep detailed records about your animal as required by my insurance company Holistic Insurance Services
Data Retention
All data will be retained for 5 years as specified by Holistic Insurance Services
Your Rights
Individuals are provided with legal rights governing the use of their personal data. These grant individuals the right to understand what personal data relating to them is held, for what purpose, how it is collected and used, with whom it is shared, where it is located, to object to its processing, to have the data corrected if inaccurate, to take copies of the data and to place restrictions on it's processing. Individuals can also request the deletion of their personal data.
Protecting Your Data
I will take all appropriate technical and organisational steps to protect the confidentiality, integrity, availability and authenticity of your data.
How to Contact Me
Please see the contact me page on this website for details.
Email:  info@back2form.co.uk
Copyright © 2020 Back2Form (Jess Harkness)
Search
Treatments When to Seek Help For Horses For Dogs and Cats Therapies Used What to Expect With Horses With Dogs and Cats FAQs Testimonials About My Background Areas Covered Treatment Costs Privacy Policy Contact Me Contact Links
